Oh!
This is awful!
I wonder if Auntie Stella and
the construction guys are okay.
Ah, looks like the guild made
it through without much damage.
It's been a while since I've
taken a good look at this.
Oh, that adventurer.
You didn't learn one decent skill?
You spent a full three-month term
practicing at every training school,
and you didn't pass one? No.
Mmm.
Kid, I'm sorry. I really am.
But I can't let you
register as an adventurer.
It was really fun to be reunited with my
instructors from back in
my first training days.
Brings back memories.
The last time I saw them
was like 15 years ago.
I'm a red light, I'm a red light.
If you're a red light,
I'll take the same time!
I'm not given any way to the world?
What do you want to see?
Let's go back to the end of the day.
If you don't want to return,
even if you don't want to?
I'm not sure if you don't want to.
I'm not sure if
you don't want to.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I want to train as a swordsman!
Train with me?
Are you sure?
Do you happen to have a permit
from the Adventurer's Guild?
I just got one from the Guildmaster!
The training is intense.
Are you prepared to
finish no matter how hard?
Yes!
That's enough!
Tomorrow will be even more intense!
He will be lucky to last three days!
It is day 10 now.
At the very least, the kid has a tenacity
that is definitely nothing to scar?
Next!
Do not drop your sword no matter what!
The enemy will not wait for you!
Hard to believe his eyes
are still so full of vigor,
even after being put
through such a brutal test.
Hmm, the kid might actually
have a promising future.
Hey, instructor!
When do you think I'll be able
to start learning a real skill?
That is not something I decide for you.
Then can you at least show me what
kind of skill I might be able to learn?
How was that, kid?
That was amazing!
Well, I couldn't see most of it.
Yes, that would figure.
It is a swift foot technique that
is even difficult for me to follow.
A boy like this probably
couldn't see much of anything.
You kept the same rhythm the entire time.
You were steady like a clock.
I caught that part.
So...
Such latent potential.
If nurtured properly, he could match me.
Or surpass me.
It's strange.
Parry!
Why has he not been able to
learn a skill aside from parry?
All he needs is one.
Just one skill that could
be considered useful.
That's enough, Noor.
Uh-huh. Unfortunately.
Wait, just give me a little more time.
Forget it.
Going further would
only be a waste of time.
A parry isn't enough for someone
to make it as a swordsman.
Swordsmanship is something he simply
doesn't have the aptitude for.
perhaps it would be wiser if you
were to choose another path who knows
your talent may be found in another
capacity there must be another
path for this child whoa whoa really
you're serious about taking part
in my training camp the swordsman
instructor told me to try something
else sig sent you huh i had heard
he was looking after a little kid
but uh he looks small enough to get
blown away by a light breeze i would
have been adventurer no matter what
a warrior's role is to become the
shield for their allies you understand
that mm-hmm okay then let's do it
i'll give the boy credit i
never thought he'd get this far
well talk about being tough and
gutsy if he could just acquire a
skill i could train this kid to be
invincible i'm sorry noor i can keep
going i acknowledge your efforts
but what you have acquired is only a
slight improvement of your natural
abilities force yourself to continue
you may very well lose your life
sorry but you'll have to move on he
toughed it out more than most he
deserves to be where his efforts are
rewarded please allow me to train
here you really want to do this kid
i do well if you insist okay here
hit that stick hanging over there
that's kind of far away
yeah yeah just do it
and once he misses i can
tell him to get lost i
can already tell he's
gonna be a huge pain in
the um was that one good
enough okay do it again
there good no no no no i want
nothing to do with this little twerp
Instructor, why am I doing nothing
but throwing rocks at stuff?
Because I just know you're going
to be too much trouble, duh.
I want to use a bow.
Now, get a good grip on
it and stand in position.
A good grip, huh?
Like this?
I am so sorry!
Trouble, trouble, trouble!
Are you serious kid that was the last
of my training bows don't break mine
my bow can handle even the strongest
just stick to throwing
stones got it okay
Who taught you to throw like that
nobody taught me this is just how i've
always hunted birds The super colorful
ones that swoop down and grab rabbits
You've got to be kidding
me that's a thunder flash
It's difficult for even the most seasoned
hunter to bring those
things down Of course,
I could totally do it with my eyes closed.
This is dumb.
There's no point in him being here.
Okay, I think I've seen enough.
Get out of here. Huh?
But I haven't learned anything yet.
I must say, you lack the prudence to
handle any sort of delicate weaponry.
You're good with rocks.
Keep doing that.
Like I said, trouble.
He doesn't need a bow.
That'd be a waste of everyone's time.
Aha.
You must be the kid
I've been hearing about.
Sure, why not? Huh? You mean it?
Come with me.
We will start right away.
Sense the enemy's presence and sneak up on
them without making a sound in your step.
Hmm.
He's not bad.
Got it!
You will have to do better than that!
There are various traps
rigged along the corridor.
Avoid setting off any of the traps and
make your way to this treasure chest.
Avoid all the traps, huh?
No problem!
Harry!
Don't go!
Incredible.
Although he...
he is missing the point of the exercise.
You failed to dismantle the traps, and
your situational awareness is abysmal.
You have no hope of becoming a spy.
That said, this boy has tenacity
that is beyond comparison.
A valuable quality.
If he ever gives up on
becoming an adventurer,
I will extend an invitation to
join the Royal Intelligence Agency.
Oh-ho!
You're quite young to be
applying for this, aren't you?
I'm pretty sure there's an age
requirement of at least 15 years old.
I already got a permit
from the Guildmaster.
I've trained at a bunch
of the other schools, too.
Didn't work out.
It seems the reason you
struggle to use magic is because
there's no mono flowing
through you in the first place.
Why does it not flow through me?
Well, perhaps you were just born that way.
In which case then,
the only hope of changing that is to
go inside the mono resonance room.
Rizzo... what?
I'm happy to give it a shot.
Well, all right.
But leave immediately if it starts
feeling too intense for you.
What?
A boy hasn't come outside yet? No, sir.
Crap, that is not good.
That room drastically amplifies all of the
human senses and he's
been in there for days.
It could kill him if we're not careful.
I'm here.
What is it?
Are you okay?
Does your body feel all right?
Yeah, I feel fine.
Just a little longer, please.
I think I'm about to have a breakthrough.
What?
This is all I've learned to do.
To think you've come this far, yet
all you can manage is tiny flame.
It's extremely rare to see someone as
incapable of magic as you seem to be, Gnor.
Now look, given your lack of mana,
it's actually impressive
how far you've come along.
What?
Am I seeing this right?
Is he dual casting?
It took me 50 years to get to that point,
yet he managed it on his
own in just three months.
I'm losing my mind.
This won't help me be an adventurer.
Indeed it won't.
Turns out this isn't the right
place for you either, is it?
Such a pity.
The kid has so much talent.
If only his body were
more attuned to magic.
He could have been known throughout
the land as an unparalleled magician.
First, let me ask you.
Did you undergo the rite of blessing
when you were a small child?
Rite of blessing?
What's that?
At this school,
only those who were selected in advance
and underwent the ceremony can train.
I'm so sorry.
Well, I don't care.
I'm not leaving until you
agree to let me train.
Do as you wish.
I'm not leaving until you
agree to let me train with you!
Fine by me.
He cannot seriously intend
to stay there forever.
I will allow you to participate
in the basics of our training.
Although please,
understand that there is no guarantee
you will actually acquire a skill.
That is most certainly low heal, but
how on earth is this even possible?
Yes, but um...
However, unfortunately for you,
low heal won't be
recognized as a serviceable
skill to make you an
accredited adventurer.
Should have known.
I can't...
I can't do anything.
Although it only works on scratches,
it's still impressive you
can use low-level healing
magic without a natural blessing
already bestowed on you.
He performed a miracle all on his own,
without undergoing the rite or
using a spirit as an intermediary.
Which, in a manner of speaking,
means he can wield the power
of miracles without limit.
Master Sane, about Noor.
He's disappeared from the capital?
I should have stopped him
while I still had the chance.
We can just leave him be, right?
That kid's strong enough
to hack it all on his own.
No.
If we help in nurturing his gifts,
then he will undoubtedly become
someone quite extraordinary.
Oh-ho!
You're right about that.
I had no idea he was going through the
same thing at all the other schools, too.
We should all give him guidance
and the training that he deserves.
That young man is overflowing
with such promise.
I have no objection.
Although it means I cannot recruit
him to the intelligence agency.
I am of the same opinion as Saiyan.
I agree.
Yeah, well, of course you would.
How about you, Sig?
I'm heading off on a search
to find him now. Hey? Whoa?
Now I understand your
eagerness but please calm down.
Now just to be clear as the sovereign
six we will all raise the boy as a group.
You all agree? Yes.
Now then let's go find this
young prodigy right away.
Well looky here? Nor?
Hey?
I'm glad you're safe. Yeah?
I made it somehow found this
lying on the ground. Oh?
It must have flown off in the attack.
Thanks a lot.
So uh?
Suppose you're well on your way to?
through already.
And then you saw what was
happening and came back. Sorta.
I heard the
news and turned around.
You're all caked in mud.
And your clothes are burnt up.
It was a hectic
day.
I kind of got into some stuff. Yeah.
Sorry to hear that.
I had a pretty bad time too.
Everybody
here is in the same boat.
What a mess.
Man, I am worn out.
I'm about that.
I hate to do this to
you, kid.
Especially since you're all beat to hell,
but the foreman was looking
all over the place for you.
He needs you to haul away some rubble
and help build some temporary housing.
That's exactly why I came by, actually.
Where
is he?
I'll get you a map. One sec.
Having you back is a huge help.
When you're here, our
progress is off the charts.
I'm glad I can still be of service.
Whew, man, what a crazy day.
I went on a ride in a
carriage, met a demon folk.
I got to fly with Lin's amazing magic,
and then I got to fly
again by Lin's magic.
And some other stuff
happened but flying around
all over the place is
what I remember most.
I'm gonna need something
to eat and get some rest
soon but no time for that
yet there's work to do.
I'm sure you already figured it
out but the theocracy of Mithra.
Were the ones working behind the scenes
with Doritas on waging this war. I did.
From the Minotaur incident to the Empire's
weaponry, the high-purity monostones,
which can only be produced in Mithra,
have been a factor at every turn.
I fear our future will not be peaceful.
However, there are people
our nation can depend on.
And most importantly,
we are blessed to have a new friend.
Oh, boy.
Instructor!
Thank you so much for
everything you did yesterday.
You're a real hero, you know that?
I know it was hard for you, but you're
still here, handing out supplies. I am.
I've also been treating those
who are injured as well.
I see you're helping with the restoration.
Yeah.
Well, you are in luck.
I'm handing these out to
everybody, so please help yourself.
Can I really? By all means.
Thanks.
I better get back to it then.
So goodbye for now. See you soon.
Okay then.
Take care, Lin. Bye!
Don't work yourself too hard, instructor.
Man, I wouldn't be where I am
without so many people's help.
Nice!
I can move so much better now.
This really is a good, sturdy sword.
It's a shame it won't see very much
flashy action with me holding on to it.
But maybe one day, I'll finally
get to be an adventurer.
And we can have epic journeys
like the heroes in the storybooks.
The ones like Dad read to me.
But for the time being, I'll
put you to good use here. Nord!
We've cleared out enough in this area!
Are you good to keep working elsewhere?
Yeah, sure, no problem.
Harry!
Oh well.
Well, I guess this is where
we really belong anyway.
I love you, I love you.
I love you, I love you. Give me.